{
    "id": "6c373c541197432f9e52b8fdcc3d5156",
    "title": "Types Of Sentences",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Soldiers were forbidden to fraternize with local citizens.",
            "description": "A sentence that has only one clause is a simple sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a lot of frantic activity just before the royal visitors arrived.",
            "description": "A complex sentence consists of one main clause and one or more dependent clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you remember the fragrance of lilacs after a rain?",
            "description": "A sentence that has only one clause is a simple sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A liking for flattery was one of his frailties.",
            "description": "A sentence that has only one clause is a simple sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Perhaps certain gifted persons can foretell the future.",
            "description": "A sentence that has only one clause is a simple sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Fold the napkins and put one by each plate.",
            "description": "A compound sentence has two or more coordinate clauses connected by a coordinating conjunction.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The preacher said that one of the brothers had strayed from the fold.",
            "description": "A complex sentence consists of one main clause and one or more dependent clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I hated the show but it has a large following.",
            "description": "A compound sentence has two or more coordinate clauses connected by a coordinating conjunction.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He eluded his followers by crossing the river.",
            "description": "A sentence that has only one clause is a simple sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Who will follow the prime minister when he retires?",
            "description": "A complex sentence consists of one main clause and one or more dependent clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The rains flooded the farmlands and destroyed all crops.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The dinner party was a flop because the guest of honor didnâ€™t show up.",
            "description": "A complex sentence consists of one main clause and one or more dependent clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}